ANIBAL CAMPOS

Summary

Motivated Full-stack web development graduate with experience working in teams to build apps from the ground up. Praised for great communication having worked with a variety of people of all walks of life. In the web development world I look forward to using my communication skills to work with people and teams to develop innovative solutions.

Employment

Fedex

2017 to 2019

Freight Handler

Managed daily freight shipments, communicating with team supervisor to surpass weekly goal of transferring 210 freight items over 2000 lbs in weight.

QuikTrip

2016 to 2017

Assistant Manager

Managed a small team, communicating(providing feedback) with team members to reach our daily goals of keeping the store looking pristine as well as keeping a safe and friendly environment for both customers and employees. Other tasks: Cash audit before taking over shift, Ordering merchandise, Run sales at the registers.

2012 to 2016

Clerk

Managed daily tasks of keeping our store spotless while providing awesome customer service. Continuous communication with other clerks and manager as well providing feedback.

Projects

Jarvis 2.0

July 2018 to July 2018

July 2018

- Game where the user must click on images without repeating a click on the same image. Images randomly reorganize themselves after each click. High Score is saved until a new high score is reached.
- Technologies: React.

Clicky-Game 2018 to 2018

- Game where the user must click on images without repeating a click on the same image. Images randomly reorganize themselves after each click. High Score is saved until a new high score is reached.
- Technologies: React.

Awards

The University of Arizona Office of Continuing & Professional Education · Full Stack Web Development

Description:

The University of Arizona Full Stack Web Development badge is given to individuals who have successfully completed an intensive coding boot camp and demonstrated a working knowledge of more than two dozen codes. They have also successfully built original, fully functional web applications.

Contact

■ anibalcampos2324@gmail.com

6024877714

♀ Phoenix. AZ

in LinkedIn

C Github

Skills

Back-End Development: Java, Api's, Node.js,

Express

FrameWorks: SpringBoot w/Maven, React Front-End Development: HTML5, CSS3,

Javascript, Bootstrap **Testing:** JUnit

Deployment: Cloud Foundry, Heroku,

Glthub pages

Databases: SQL, NoSQL

Code Management: Git, Glthub, Ubuntu/shell,

Gitbash/shell

Education

Tech Talent South

Apr. 2019 to July 2019

480 hours in person Full-Stack Web Development program

Glendale Community College Aug. 2010 to May 2012

Pre-Nursing

University of Arizona Jan. 2018 to July 2018

240 hours in person Full Stack Web Development Certification Program